Felipe Costa Godoi Uberaba – MG – Brazil

feeh.08.2001@gmail.com

Single

Neighborhood: Santa Maria - Uberaba

12/01/2001

Phone: +55 34 997651567

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/felipe-godoi

Website: https://godoi.dev

OBJECTIVE: Back-end Developer

Education

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Engineering – Instituto Federal do Triângulo Mineiro (IFTM). Postgraduate Lato Sensu, Specialization in Blockchain Development – UniFECAF Postgraduate Lato Sensu, Specialization in Distributed Systems Architecture – PUC Minas

QUALIFICATION SUMMARY

I have been developing since I was 14 but began my professional career at 18. I have over 4 years of experience in software development. During this time, I have primarily worked as a full-stack developer with a focus on back-end, engaging in all necessary areas: front-end, back-end, infrastructure, databases, etc. I have always been driven by a strong curiosity to learn different technologies. My main experience includes Node and Angular, but I have also worked with Python, C#, Rust, Java, and most recently, I have been studying Web3 with Solidity. I hold a Bachelor's degree in Computer Engineering and am currently pursuing postgraduate specializations in Distributed Software Architecture and Blockchain Development.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

TALENT ACADEMY - May 2022 - Present

Backend Developer (Node.is)

Responsibilities include enhancement and maintenance of a web platform used for Digital HR solutions. I address bug fixes, discuss architectures and technologies, and develop new tools. Technologies used: Node.js, Angular, MySQL, GCP.

DPROWARE, YOUR SOFTWARE FACTORY – February 2021 – April 2022

Backend Developer (Node.js)

Provided consultancy for companies as a software factory. Worked with various clients to develop integrations between their logistic systems and point of sale, in addition to providing general technological solutions. Technologies used: Node.js, Angular, .NET Framework, React, Ionic, SQL Server, Windows Server.

MULLTIPLA MANAGEMENT PLATFORM FOR DISTRIBUTORS AND INDUSTRIES— January 2020 – February 2021

Backend Developer Intern (Node.js)

Developed an app for logistics and WMS. Led the development of the app architecture and the APIs that processed and managed data received by logistic systems. Technologies used: Node.js, SQL Server, Ionic, Angular, Windows Server.

PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT

SOLID with Java: Object-Oriented Programming Principles – Alura

GPT and Python: Creating Tools with the API – Alura

Exploring Vue3 Framework – Alura

NestJS from Scratch with TypeORM, Mongoose, Prisma, and Swagger – Udemy

The Complete Python Course | Learn Python by Doing in 2024 – Udemy

Ethereum Development Fundamentals – 101 Blockchains

Solidity Fundamentals – 101 Blockchains

Bitcoin Programming - UniFECAF